CITYU CS + NCTU CS RYAN YEN

Phone: (+886) 975053949

Email: ryanyen89@gmail.com · GitHub: https://github.com/ryanyen2

Diligent and quick learner who is finding a one-year placement internship for year-three. I am capable of being a **front-end** and as well as **back-end developer**. Focusing on cutting-edge development techniques and have pixel-perfect spirit.

EXPERIENCE

06/2020 - 06/2021

FRONT-END-DEVELOPER & PROJECT MANAGER, NETWORLD TECH LTD.

One-Year Placement of Networld Ltd. (HTTPS://WWW.NETWORLD.HK/)

Focusing on web and App development and management for the newest product.

Represented as the branch between HK and Taiwan for Networld to get into TW's market.

09/2019 - NOW

WEB-DEVELOPER, CITYU IT TEAM

Web developer and maintainer of website for several CityU IT related competitions and events. Creating website for different organizer, sponsor such as CityU, AWS, Wizlynx.

06/2019 - 07/2019

PROJECT MANAGER ASSISTANT, ASUS

Assistant project manager and RD to interact with the user-end and report errors for the unreleased product – ZenBook Duo.

EDUCATION

09 2018 ~ 06 2022

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, CITY UNIVERSITY OF HK

GPA 3.84 (straight A) on all CS related courses

4-year full scholarship ~ \$500,000.00 HKD

Winning 2 other scholarship for summer exchange to **Stanford** and Czech Republic.

Previous **Best Programmer** on CityU online judge system.

03 2020 ~ 06 2022

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, NCTU TAIWAN 國立交通大學

Working on several competitions such as **ACM/ICPC** & **Google Code Jam** Applying to the organizer of **Hackathon** competition in Northern Taiwan.

07 2019 ~ 08 2019

SUMMER SCHOOL OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF HRADEC KRALOVE

Supported and funded by department of Electricial engineering to Czech Republic to study for the summer school and learn the basic **App development** for Android by **Kotlin, Android Studio**.

09 2015 ~ 06 2018

SCIENCE & ENGINEER MAJOR, TAIPEI LISHAN SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

Holding over 20 receptions for school

Being a School Representative Ambassador

Assigned to various countries for **academic and technical exchange** (ex: Malaysia, Vietnam, Japan .etc.)

Top 3% among the **GSAT** (Taiwanese **university entrance exam**, 10 subjects in total) Selected as the school represented **member of Rotary Club**

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership skill
 - Leading over 10 teams to participate in several competitions and events
- Strategic Planning Skill/Logistic Trouble Shooter/Time Manager
- Discipline Self-Learner
- Communication Skill/ Great Team Player
- Excellent English / Chinese speaking and writing skill

HARD SKILLS

• Front-end:

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / Vue.JS/ Node.JS / AWS/ Kotlin

• Back-end:

C++ / Python / Java / SQL

Container:

Docker

• Excellent in Microsoft Tools: PowerPoint / Word / Excel

ACTIVITIES

COMPETITIONS

Alibaba Entrepreneurs Fund's Jump starter
Deloitte Hackathon Competition
YDC Business Pitch Competition
team leader/ semi-final
team leader/ second round
Tencent HK Fintech Competition
team leader

EVENTS & EXCHANGES

5. **Summer Exchange** to Czech Republic (2 months)

Learning Kotlin & Android Studio to develop a simple game

6. Organizer of **AWSome Day**

Working with AWS Taiwan team, providing a website and advertising the event

7. Cyberport Creative Micro Fund Program

Having two weeks startup courses and activities in Shenzhen which is sponsored by Cyberport

8. Organizer of **Wizlynx group IT Sharing**

Working with Wizlynx group, organizing a seminar about cybersecurity industry

TEAMS

- 9. <u>IEEE-Eta-Kappa-Nu Club</u>
- 10. Taiwan MC Hackathon Development Team
- 11. CityU Robotic Team
- 12. Hall 2 IT Team
- 13. Business Proposal and Competition Club
- 14. Athletic and Aquatic Team